needforseatusa.com 2014-11-28

# NEEDforSEAT USA's privacy policy

The protection of your private information is very important to us. The following details how we handle your confidential data.

Acquisition, processing and utilization of personal dataAll pages of our website (except for account details) are available without providing personal information.

We only save access data with no personal connection, such as the requesting host address (IP of the computer), the web page you are using to visit us or the name of the requested file. This information is used only to evaluate our offer, and we are not able to draw any personal references from it. Personal data are raised only in the context of your goods order, with opening of a customer account or with registration for our news type character voluntarily to communicate.

We use your data without your explicit permission solely for the functioning and execution of this service.

With the full execution of the contract and the complete payment of the buying price, your data will be blocked for further use and after the expiry of the legal fiscal and commercial regulations be deleted, as far as you did not explicitly agree to the further use of your data. If you register for our newsletter by means of your email address, we use your email address for internal advertising purposes until you unsubscribe from our newsletter.

You may unsubscribe at any time.

## Use of Cookies

In this shop, information concerning the content of your shopping basket is stored in the Cookies so that this can then be called up the next time your visit the site. If you register on our website or wish to send an order, we require your customer data. Since the data is generated by the cookies, you do not need to fill out forms. In their browser programme customers may also manage the acceptance of cookies on this page and block them if they wish.

## Transfer of personal data

If necessary, we will pass on your data to our shipping company. For the processing of payments, we must pass along the relevant data to the authorized banking institution.

## Right to information

You have the right to free information about your stored data at any time as well as the right to correct, lock or delete this data.

## Contact party for privacy issues

For questions concerning collection, processing or use of your personal information or for questions concerning accessing of information, amendments, suspension or deletion of data, as well as repealing of previously given authorization, please use the form on our contact page. You may also contact us by postal mail using the address provided on that page. 

## Revocation of the consent

The following consent you gave (if necessary) in the process of ordering may be withdrawn at any time.

## Trademarks

MAXNOMIC™ and NEEDforSEAT® and their logos are trademarks of the owner Marco Woerenkaemper in Germany, USA and other countries.The use of the trademarks without the prior written consent of the trademark owner, Marco Woerenkaemper is not permitted.If you have any questions about our brands and the use, please contact to above mentioned contact details.
